[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can create this distressed text
您可以创建此痛苦的文本
effect
效应
using inkscape but before we get started
使用Inkscape，但在我们开始之前
if you'd like to learn more about how
如果您想了解更多有关如何
inkscape works be sure to check out my
Inkscape作品一定要查看我的
inkscape master class
Inkscape大师班
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where i go over every tool and feature
在那里我检查了每一个工具和功能
in inkscape
在Inkscape
and i explain what it is and demonstrate
我解释了它是什么，并展示了
how it works i'll have a link in the
它是如何工作的，我会在
description of the video if you want to
视频描述(如果您想要
check that out
看看这个
so to get us started here in inkscape
为了让我们从Inkscape开始
the first thing we want to do is set up
我们要做的第一件事是设置
our document so that we are all working
我们的文件，所以我们都在工作
with a similar workflow
使用类似的工作流程
to do that i'll come up here to where it
为了做到这一点，我会来到这里
says view make sure we have custom
说VIEW确保我们有客户
selected
已选择
and then go to zoom and where it says go
然后转到缩放和它显示的去向
to view zoom and we're looking for zoom
来查看变焦，我们正在寻找变焦
one to one
一对一
like that and for this tutorial we're
就像这样，在本教程中，我们将
going to want to disable snapping which
我想要禁用哪种捕捉
is up here this
就在这上面
icon in the top left hand corner just
位于左上角的图标
click on that to disable it
单击该选项可将其禁用
if you already have it deselected then
如果您已将其取消选中，则
you're good to go and then finally we
你可以走了，然后我们终于
want to open up the fill and stroke menu
我想打开填充和描边菜单
which is over here
它就在这里
or you could press the uh you could
或者你可以按，呃，你可以
press ctrl shift and f on the keyboard
按键盘上的Ctrl Shift和f键
to open that up
把它打开
so the first thing i'm going to do is
所以我要做的第一件事是
create some text so let me grab the text
创建一些文本，让我抓起文本
tool over here
工具在这里
click on the canvas and for this
在画布上单击，并为此
tutorial i'm just going to use a capital
教程我要用一个大写字母
letter g
字母g
you can use whatever letter or number
你可以用任何字母或数字
you want though
不过，你想要
and i'm going to change the font of this
我要改变这个的字体
i'm going to click on the text editor up
我要向上点击文本编辑器
here this little t
这是这只小T
icon and i'm going to change this to
图标，我要将其更改为
league
联盟
gothic you don't have to use this font
哥特式，你不必使用这种字体
you could use whatever font you'd like
你可以使用任何你喜欢的字体
it should work just fine with this
它应该可以用这个很好地工作
tutorial and let me grab the select tool
教程，让我拿起选择工具
over here
在这里
and let me just scale this up oops not
让我把它放大，哦，不是
like that let me grab this arrow right
就像这样，让我抓住这个箭头
here then hold ctrl
在这里，然后按住Ctrl
to lock the proportions put this towards
要锁定比例，请将此设置为
the center of the page scale it up a
页面的中心将其放大
little more
再多一点
that's looking pretty good and now what
看起来很不错，现在怎么办？
i want to do is convert this from a text
我想要做的是将它从文本转换为
object to a path so that we can edit it
对象添加到路径，以便我们可以对其进行编辑
further
进一步
to do that i'll go to path object to
为此，我将转到Path Object to
path
路径
and then click on the ungroup button
然后点击Ungroup按钮
over here which is uh this icon that
在这里，呃，是这个图标，
says ungroup or you could
说解组，或者你可以
press ctrl shift and g
按Ctrl Shift和g
now i will take the opacity and bring
现在我要把不透明带到
this down roughly in half
这个数字大约减半
and in order to give this the distressed
为了给这个痛苦的人
effect we're going to do two different
效果我们要做两个不同的
things to it
关于它的事情
number one we're going to roughen the
第一，我们要粗略地
edges so it looks more whimsical
边缘，让它看起来更奇特
and number two we're going to add a
第二，我们将添加一个
vector texture to the center of the
将纹理矢量到
letter here
信封在此
so starting first with the the rough the
所以先从粗略的开始
roughened edges to do that i'm going to
为了做到这一点，我要
grab the edit paths by nodes tool
抓取按结点编辑路径工具
and what we're looking at is the number
我们现在看到的是这个数字
of nodes here in the letter if you
字母中的节点，如果您
notice
通知
during in this curve over here we have a
在这条曲线上，我们有一个
lot of nodes but in this straight line
有很多节点，但在这条直线上
we don't have
我们没有
very many nodes at all so what we want
非常多的节点，所以我们想要的
to do is add some new nodes in here
要做的是在此处添加一些新节点
by double clicking these lines so that
通过双击这些行，以便
it's more consistent with the rest of
它与其他的更一致
the design
设计
because the way we're going to roughen
因为我们要粗暴对待
these edges is by altering the position
这些边是通过改变位置来实现的
of these nodes using an extension which
使用扩展的这些节点的
i'm going to show you in just a minute
我马上就给你们展示一下
so
所以
go ahead and add some new nodes where
继续并添加一些新节点，其中
they are needed so that it looks more
它们是需要的，这样它看起来更像
consistent all the way through maybe
可能自始至终始终如一
i'll put one here
我会在这里放一个
another one right here
另一个就在这里
and i'd say that's looking pretty good
我要说的是这看起来很不错
right there so we'll go back to the
就在那里，所以我们将回到
select tool
选择工具
what i want to do now is go to
我现在想做的是去
extensions modify path
扩展修改路径
and click on jitter nodes and i'm going
然后点击抖动节点，我就可以
to use these presets right here
要在此处使用这些预设
1.0 1.0 shift node selected
已选择1.0 1.0 Shift节点
shift node handles deselected uniform
Shift节点控制柄取消选择统一
and go ahead and click live preview to
然后继续并单击实时预览以
see how it looks
看看它看起来怎么样
now the numbers that you should use here
现在，您应该在这里使用的数字
depend entirely on the size of your
完全取决于您的
letter if you notice here
如果你注意到这里有信的话
displacing these two axis at one pixel
在一个像素上移动这两个轴
is perfect it looks good right there if
是完美的，如果它在那里看起来很好
this were too high let's say if i had
这太高了，比方说如果我
something like 10
大概10个左右
it would look something like that or
它会看起来像这样，或者
that's not that's not that's that's too
不是，太棒了
much it doesn't even look like a letter
它甚至看起来都不像一封信
anymore so i want to lower that to 1.
所以我想把它降到1。
now i'm mentioning this because you're
现在我提到这件事是因为你
probably going to have to use a
可能将不得不使用
different value
不同的价值
other than one in order to get this
而不是一个人，为了得到这个
result so make sure to play around with
结果，所以一定要玩一玩
these numbers a little bit to see what
这些数字稍微看看是什么
gets the best result
获得最佳结果
what we're looking for is this right
我们要找的就是这个
here where the edges just look a little
这里的边缘看起来有点
roughened like that that's perfect as it
像这样粗制滥造，太完美了
is so
是这样吗？
i'll click apply then close out of that
我将单击应用，然后关闭该窗口
and now we want to do is apply a texture
现在我们要做的是应用一种纹理
to this letter
致此信
but i don't want to apply the texture to
但我不想将纹理应用于
the entire letter i want it
我想要整封信
to only be applied to the center of the
仅应用于
letter here the middle portion so i'm
字母在中间部分，所以我是
going to create a duplicate of this
我要创建此文件的副本
letter and then offset it
字母，然后对齐它
to make it smaller and then use that as
把它变小，然后把它当作
the reference selection
参考选择
for applying the texture so i'm going to
用于应用纹理，所以我要
right click this object and go to
右键单击此对象并转到
duplicate
复本
and i'm going to make this green just so
我要把它变成绿色的
we can differentiate it
我们可以区分它
and i'm going to come up here to where
我要到这里来，
it says path and i'm going to click on
它显示PATH，我将点击
simplify to get rid of some of those
简化以去掉其中的一些
nodes that we added
我们添加的节点
and then we'll come over here and go to
然后我们会来到这里，去
path and i will look for
小路和我会去寻找
dynamic offset and now i want to take
动态偏移，现在我想要
this little node up here and just bring
这里的这个小节点就是
this down
把这个放下来
so that we have this smaller version of
所以我们有这个更小的版本
the letter
这封信
inside of it like that and that green
在它里面，像这样和那个绿色
area that's where we want the texture to
这是我们希望纹理所在的区域
be applied
被应用
so let's finalize that by going to path
因此，让我们通过转到Path来结束这一点
object to path
对象到路径
go back to the select tool and now what
返回到选择工具，现在怎么办
i want to do is import a vector texture
我想要做的是导入一个矢量纹理
i will have this linked in the
我会把这个链接到
description of the video to where you
视频的描述，您可以在其中
can go and download this svg texture so
我可以去下载这个SVG纹理
you can work with it i'm just going to
你可以用它，我正要去
open up the folder here on my other
打开我的另一台电脑上的文件夹
monitor and uh
监视器和呃
well i'll show you over here i have this
好的，我带你去看看，我有这个
open like this i'm going to take this
像这样打开，我要拿着这个
scratch.svg and i'm just going to click
Scratch.svg，我只需点击
and drag that into inkscape like that
像这样把它拖到Inkscape中
and it's going to ask all of this stuff
它会问所有这些问题
i'm just going to leave the defaults
我只需要保留默认设置
click ok
单击“确定”
and there is our let me zoom out a
还有我们的让我放大一个
little bit to zoom out i'm going to hold
稍微缩小一点，我会保持不变
ctrl and roll down the mouse wheel
按Ctrl键并向下滚动鼠标滚轮
there is our vector texture now let me
这是我们的矢量纹理，现在让我
position this over the green area if you
如果您将其放置在绿色区域上，请
notice where the red
注意红色的地方
and the green are intersecting that's
和果岭相交，这是
going to be the area where the
将会是一个区域
the texture is applied to the letter so
该纹理应用于字母，因此
i just want to make sure i have it
我只想确认我有没有
positioned where i want it
放置在我想要的位置
that right there looks pretty good so
就在那里，看起来很不错，所以
i'm going to hold i'm going to click on
我要等一下，我要点击
this green letter to select that
这个绿色字母来选择那个
and then i'm going to hold shift and
然后我要按住班次
click on the red texture
点击红色纹理
and with them both selected i'll go to
选择了这两个选项后，我将转到
path intersection
小路交叉口
and then i'll hold shift and click on
然后我会按住Shift键并点击
the letter and go to path
这封信和去小路
difference and what we can do now is
不同的是我们现在能做的是
bring the opacity all the way back up
将不透明度调高至最高
and zoom out and as you can see we are
缩小，如你所见，我们是
finished that is how you can
完成了，这就是你可以
pretty easily create a distressed text
很容易就会创建一个痛苦的文本
effect using inkscape so
使用Inkscape So的效果
if you have any questions just leave a
如果您有任何问题，请在
comment below and as always thanks for
在下面发表评论，并一如既往地感谢
watching
观看
[Music]
[音乐]